When students are taking AEP courses,
生徒がAEPコースを受講している場合、
their teachers do many things
生徒の学力向上の助けるため、
to help them improve their academic skills.
教師陣はさまざまなことを行います。
AEP teachers teach both language and content together.
AEPの教師は、英語とその日の授業の要点を教えます。
Students then practice the language
生徒たちは、習った要点に沿って
in a meaningful way using the content learned.
効率的に英語の練習を行っていきます。
Students learn to think critically
この学習方法を通じて、生徒は
about a variety of academic topics
さまざまなトピックについて、論理的な思考を学びつつ
and then are taught how to express their ideas orally or in writing
口頭や文章で自分のアイデアを
using effective strategies.
効果的に表現する方法を、学びます。
Scaffolding a lesson is often used
このような授業の指導要綱は、
to support students with weaker English than their classmates.
英語力が低い生徒達にとって効果的です。
Teaching strategies are used to manage a multi-level class.
また、それぞれの教師は、レベルに応じて、指導方法を変えて授業を進行させます。
In AEP classes, the teacher
AEPクラスでは、
teaches all four skills (reading, writing, speaking, listening)
すべてのクラスで4つのスキル（リーディング、ライティング、スピーキング、リスニング）を教え
in every class and students will practice them.
生徒は日々、練習をします。
The teacher includes a new or reviewed grammar point
教師は新しい文法、また今までに授業にでてきた文法を織り交ぜ、
each day for students to practice
日々の学習を興味深ものにするように心がけ、
and makes the lessons interesting so students stay motivated
生徒が学習へのモチベーションを保てるように工夫します。
The teacher teaches students many new academic words
教師は学習内容に沿った多くの語彙、
and important information that will prepare them for academic classes
アカデミックプログラムに役立つ重要な情報を生徒に与えます。
He or she gives students many opportunities
生徒が興味を持つような本読みを行い、読解力を高める様、
to read interesting books and write on important topics
本の重要なトピックをまとめ、文章に書かせたり、
and gives them many opportunities to speak on different topics
ディスカッションを行う機会を提供します。
The teacher gives the students a lot of homework
また、教師は多くの宿題を生徒に与えることで、
so they can practice the skills learned in class
授業中に学んだスキルの練習できるよう、
and expects their students to read every day for 45 minutes
生徒が一日最低45分は、英語で読書する機会をあたえます。
The teachers gives students a lot of feedback
ボドウェルでは、教師は生徒に多くのフィードバックを与えます。
so they know what to work on inside and outside of class
授業の内外で何をすべきかを理解し、
and helps students understand how they are assessed
採点方法を、生徒が理解することで、
so they can monitor their own progress
生徒自身が自分の進捗状況を、図ることができます。
Also, the teacher uses assessment FOR learning,
また、ボドウェルでは、
which is formative
点数だけでの評価
assessment AS learning which, is self-assessment.
(サマティブ・アセスメント)ではなく、
And assessment OF learning which is summative,
生徒の弱点などを具体的にあげ、フィードバックを与え
to help student progress and succeed.
英語力上達を助けることを目的とする評価方法（フォーマティブ・アセスメント）も取り入れています。